

HENDRI YUSDA TANJUNG

Address: Perumnas Helvetia, Medan Helvetia, Kota Medan, SUMUT

Phone: +6285270363439

Email: hendri.yusda01@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/hendritanjung

SUMMARY

My work experience at PT. Telkomsel as an IT Operation professional has enriched my understanding of telecommunications technology and the high demands of adapting to rapid changes in this industry. I have taken on roles in developing systems and applications that support the company's core operations, including customer management, data analysis, and customer service.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Operation, Developer

July 2021 - Present

- Development of sales data applications and dashboard summary using chart graphs.
- rocessing Company Big Data for Visualization and Analysis.
- Creation of robots for WiFi scanning and room temperature measurement.
- Server data visualization using Grafana.

Website development services

Jan 2012 - Mei 2021

I used to be a freelance web programmer. As a web programmer, I have developed expertise in various programming languages. I have designed attractive user interfaces and layouts, as well as developed essential functionalities for websites, such as forms, interactivity, database integration, and more.

Administrasi Dokumen Feb 2012 - Jun 2012

As part of the administrative team, I have experience managing thousands of taxpayer identification (NPWP) data and efficiently organizing documents, creating a system that simplifies data retrieval for audit and reporting purposes.

EDUCATION

Universitas Potensi Utama

Sep 2013 - Nov 2017

S1 - Sistem Informasi

SMK Negeri 9 Medan

May 2011 - May 2013

Software Engineering

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Python, AWK, SSH, C++
- Data: Mysql, PostgreSQL, Mongodb, Prometheus.
- Framework: Codeingiter, Laraverl, JQuery, Bootstrap
- Visualisasi Data: Grafana and Highchart.
- . OS: LINUX and ROS

ACTIVITIES

- · Development of robots for additional sensor implementation
- · Data visualization from Al-based applications